const daySixQuestions = [
  {
    question: "When did the Battle of Badr take place?",
    options: ["1 AH", "2 AH", "3 AH", "570 AD"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first mosque built by the Holy Prophet?",
    options: ["Masjid Quba", "Masjid Nabawi", "Masjid Bilal", "Masjid Al Aqsa"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Azan was introduced during the first year of Hijrah. Who was appointed as the first Muezzan?",
    options: [
      "Hazrat Ali RA",
      "Abu Bakr RA",
      "Prophet Muhammad SAW",
      "Hazrat Bilal RA",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many Muslims were killed by the army of infidels in the Battle of Badr?",
    options: ["313", "314", "14", "15"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was an assistant to Prophet Musa ('Aalayhi Salaam)?",
    options: ["Isa AS", "Haroon AS", "Dawood AS", "Isaac AS"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "When was Prophet Muhammad (s.a.w) born?",
    options: ["560 AD", "570 AD", "580 AD", "1 AH"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "In which battle was Hamzah, the Prophet's uncle, killed?",
    options: ["Hunayn", "Uhud", "Khandaq", "Badr"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the capital of Abbasyid Khalifah?",
    options: ["Qurtuba", "Medina", "Mecca", "Baghdad"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Battle is also called the Battle of Confederates?",
    options: [
      "Battle of Badr",
      "Battle of Uhud",
      "Battle of Ghajwa",
      "Battle of Trench",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  // Additional Questions
  {
    question: "What is the significance of the year 1 AH in Islamic history?",
    options: [
      "The year of the Hijra (Migration) of Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) to Medina",
      "The year of the Battle of Badr",
      "The year of the Treaty of Hudaybiyyah",
      "The year of the Prophet's Night Journey (Isra and Miraj)",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which city was the capital of the Umayyad Caliphate?",
    options: ["Kufa", "Damascus", "Cairo", "Cordoba"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
];
export default daySixQuestions;
